MEN: Will you be making the trip out to Los Angeles next Monday?
WOMAN: I was planning to, but something has come up,
so I was contemplating whether or not I should delay my trip to the week after. Why do you ask?
MEN: My brother who moved to France five years ago is coming to LA next week on a business trip,
so I was thinking of going out there to see him.
And since I heard you are going, I thought maybe we could drive down together.
WOMAN: That sounds like a good idea.
I do have to make a trip there, and it would be nice to have some company.
Hmm... tell you what, I will see what I can do to take the trip next week after all.
Let me give you a shout with the details after lunch today.